jasonsdeli.com 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Jason's Deli

**Last Updated: June 8, 2016**

Jason's Deli’s policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users.  Jason’s Deli and its affiliates, subsidiaries, and divisions (collectively, “Company,” “we” or “us”) respects your personal privacy and is committed to adhering to federal and state privacy laws and industry guidelines in order to protect you and your identity.  This privacy policy (“Policy” or “Privacy Policy”) describes how we handle the information of users of the Jason’s Deli website and/or our Mobile Applications (collectively, the “Website” or “Site”).  Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using the Site. 

If you are unwilling to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, we ask that you do not use the Site.  By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to occasionally update this Privacy Policy. At such time, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Policy.

  1. **Children Under 13**

The Site is not intended for, or designed to attract, children under the age of 13; it is also not intended, or designed, to collect personal information from children.  If a parent or guardian has reason to believe that a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian should contact us at [customer.service@jasonsdeli.com](mailto:customer.service@jasonsdeli.com).   

  1. **Information We May Collect from You**

  1. _Information You Provide:_   From time to time, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, location, local Jason’s Deli restaurant, payment information, and other comparable information.  Providing this information will always be voluntary, and your information will always be used for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy.
  2. _Internet Protocol (IP) Address & Location Information:_  When you use the Site, we may passively collect (that is, gather without you actively providing the information) your IP address and the location from which you are visiting the Site.  We may aggregate this information with similar information provided by other users to produce analytics regarding the number of users visiting a site from a particular location, for instance, or to sort your search results by the restaurant closest to you.  The data we collect will never contain, or be combined with, information that identifies you personally without your permission.
  3. _Other Passive Information Collection:_   We and/or our service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and technology providers may use session and persistent cookies, web beacons, clear gifs, session IDs, successor tracker technology and other similar technologies as you navigate the Site and material displayed thereon.  “Cookies,” for instance, are small text files placed on your Internet browser in order to perform functions like tracking your preferences and selections as you navigate the Site, showing you advertisements based on your interests, or gathering information about the technology you are using to access the Site.  We passively collect this information to understand what areas of the Site are most popular, which areas may require improvement and what technologies are being used by our visitors.  This information helps us and the aforementioned third parties to update and improve the Site and otherwise manage and measure the performance of content, promotions, advertisements and other features displayed or delivered on or through the Site.  We also use this information for security purposes, to detect and to block security breaches and to provide you with a safe online environment.  Many web browsers will allow you to disable or block cookies and other similar technologies, but please note that doing so may prevent you from using certain parts or features of the Site, or prevent the Site from working properly for you.
  4. _Information from Other Sources:_   From time to time, we may also obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners and independent third-party sources and add it to other information about you.  We may also use third-party information to supplement, or verify the accuracy of, information already contained in our records. The Site may also contain functionality which enables you to import profile information or contacts from third party services, including social media services (e.g., LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, Gmail, Google+, FourSquare, Instagram, Vine, etc.).  Any data maintained by such third-party service and your use of that third-party service will be subject to that third party’s terms of use and privacy policy.  You may have the ability to post information from the Site to your third-party accounts.  All such postings are also subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of the applicable third parties as well as the terms of this Privacy Policy.
  5. _Mobile Location Services_ : The Mobile Applications may also include location functionality that relies upon collection of geo-location data from your mobile device (e.g., to identify nearby Jason’s Deli locations).  Your mobile device may include settings to disable the Mobile Application’s access to your location.  Please check your device and/or operating system instructions for availability and details.  Note, however, that opting out of the Mobile Application’s collection of location information will cause its location-based features to be disabled. 

  1. **How the Company may Use and Disclose Information Obtained through the Service**

  1. _Our Use:_   We may use the information collected to provide you services related to the Jason’s Deli experience.  Your information may be used by the Site to provide notifications and messages to you (including information about our products or services).  Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected internally to operate the services described on the Site (including to fulfill online food orders, process payments, etc.), to improve the Site, to customize the Site to your preferences, to communicate information to you, for research purposes and for any other purpose specified in this Policy.  We may also use your information to display advertising in the Site to our advertisers’ target audiences.  In addition, we may make full use of all information acquired through the Site that is not in personally identifiable form.
  2. _Other Company Disclosures:_   We may disclose any of the information you provide:

  1. to service providers we use to support our business (such as hosting providers, technical support, data analytics, mailing houses and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to use it for the same purposes;
  2. in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, reorganization, assignment or other transfer of the Company or the business of the Site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;
  3. to respond to law enforcement requests and subpoenas, where we believe in good faith that such response is required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations; and
  4. in situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person.

We do not otherwise distribute to third parties your personally identifiable information.The Company, however, will have no liability for disclosure of information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized intervention of third parties except as required by law.

  1. **Choices You May Have About How We Use Your Information**

If you have provided us with information identifying you personally and wish to update, correct or delete it from our records, please notify us of your wishes by logging on to the Website and accessing your current information under the "My Profile" menu selection.  You may edit or remove addresses on file, update your name or telephone numbers, change your email address, opt-in or opt-out for email communications or change your password.  Alternatively, you may contact us at [customer.service@jasonsdeli.com](mailto:customer.service@jasonsdeli.com).  Where it is possible to do so, we will act on your request to amend or delete your personal information within a reasonable time.   However, such modifications or deletions may only affect reports after the date of such modifications; any data associated with prior reports may remain unmodified as previously provided to recipients of that data and stored in our servers.

  1. **How the Company Protects Your Information**

We work hard to protect the integrity of the information collected in our databases.  We use both technical and procedural methods to maintain the integrity and security of our databases, including the use of encryption and limited access to data.  But you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free.  PLEASE NOTE:  The safety and security of your information also depends on you.  Never share your password with anyone else, notify us promptly if you believe your password security has been breached, and remember to log off of the Site before you leave your computer or mobile device.

  1. **Contacting Third Parties**

If you elect to contact any third party identified on this Site, whether directly or through links, your choice to provide that party with your personal information is solely at your discretion.  We have no control over, and are not responsible for, any collection or use of your information by such third parties.

  1. **How You Can Contact the Company**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices related to this Site, please contact us at [customer.service@jasonsdeli.com](mailto:customer.service@jasonsdeli.com).  You may always opt out of receiving communications from us by clicking on the removal link provided at the bottom of every email sent by us.

  1. **Information Collected Elsewhere**

This Policy applies only to information collected on this Website and through our Mobile Applications; it does not apply to information collected in other areas, whether online or offline.  This Policy does not apply to third-party websites that may be accessed through a link on the Site. You should review the privacy policies of any third-party websites to understand how those sites collect, use and disclose any information. 

  1. **This Website’s Response to Browser “Do Not Track” Signals**

Our Website does not respond to pre-set browser “do not track” signals or similar mechanisms that provide users with choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information relating to online activities over time and across third-party websites.  Once the Internet industry has settled on standards related to this issue and Company recognizes such standards, we may reevaluate this approach.
